I Love Rock 'n' Roll
I saw him dancin' there by the record machine
I knew he must have been about seventeen
The beat was goin' strong playin' my favorite song
And I could tell it wouldn't be long
Till he was with me, yeah me and
I could tell it wouldn't be long 'till he was with me, yeah me
Singin' I love rock 'n roll so put another dime in the jukebox baby
I love rock 'n roll so come and take your time and dance with me aw
He smiled so
I got up and asked for his name
That don't matter he said 'cos it's all the same
He said can
I take you home where we can be alone and next we were movin' on
And he was with me, yeah me next we were movin' on and he was with me, yeah me
Singin' I love rock 'n roll so put another dime in the jukebox baby
I love rock 'n roll so come and take your time and dance with me aw
He said can
I take you home where we can be alone next we were movin' on
And he was with me, yeah me and were we movin' on and singing that same old song yeah with me
Singin' I love rock 'n roll so put another dime in the jukebox baby
I love rock 'n roll so come and take your time and dance with me
I love rock 'n roll so put another dime in the jukebox baby
I love rock 'n roll so come and take your time and dance with
I love rock 'n roll so come and take your time and dance with me
I love rock 'n roll so put another dime in the jukebox baby